Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Trisexual Books
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Trisexual books
1982-1988
Bailey 6
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
120 v.; 17-18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, other transgender activity, and lesbian and gay erotics.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, other transgender activity, and lesbian and gay erotics.
Some individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Some titles include personal advertisements.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Lesbians -- Fiction; Gay men -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Personals -- United States; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Trisexual Books
  - Blind date, c1982; TR_101_ (Box 101-128)
  - Secret fantasy, c1982; TR_102_ (Box 101-128)
  - Suburban wives, c1982; TR_103_ (Box 101-128)
  - Humiliated jock, c1982; TR_104_ (Box 101-128)
  - Shameful display, c1982; TR_105_ (Box 101-128)
  - Lesbian threesome, c1982; TR_106_ (Box 101-128)
  - Pretty boy, c1982; TR_107_ (Box 101-128)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - She-male lover, c1982; TR_108_ (Box 101-128)
  - Proud Mary, c1982; TR_109_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite submission, c1982; TR_110_ (Box 101-128)
  - Drag queen, c1982; TR_111_ (Box 101-128)
    Undeciphered stamp on top edge
  - TV show girl, c1982; TR_112_ (Box 101-128)
    Stamp on top edge: SNG[?]
  - Madames TV slave, c1982; TR_113_ (Box 101-128)
  - Dressing up Bobby, c1982; TR_114_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover: Special $2.00 each.
  - She-male honey, c1982; TR_115_ (Box 101-128)
  - Pretty boy in panties, c1982; TR_116_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover, slightly obscuring title: Special $2.00 each.
  - Shamed schoolboy, c1983; TR_117_ (Box 101-128)
  - She-male model, c1983; TR_118_ (Box 101-128)
    "Copy 1: Price label on front cover: Special $2.00 each. Copy 2: Stamp on bottom edge: 5"
  - Serving sisters, c1983; TR_119_ (Box 101-128)
  - Twin delights, c1983; TR_120_ (Box 101-128)
  - High school transvestite, c1983; TR_121_ (Box 101-128)
  - Crossdressed tycoon, c1983; TR_122_ (Box 101-128)
  - The boy next door, c1983; TR_123_ (Box 101-128)
    Back cover detached
  - Teen stud in panties, c1983; TR_124_ (Box 101-128)
  - Dresses for her brother, c1983; TR_125_ (Box 101-128)
  - Forced to be a girl, c1983; TR_126_ (Box 101-128)
  - Husband's lingerie fetish, c1983; TR_127_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite maid, c1983; TR_128_ (Box 101-128)
  - Training daddy, c1983; TR_129_ (Box 129-155)
  - Momma's baby doll, c1983; TR_130_ (Box 129-155)
    Copy 2: Printed label for "CDL Mail Order" affixed to mail order form at very end of book, obscuring the original printed ordering address for Star Distributors
  - The girl next door, c1983; TR_131_ (Box 129-155)
  - She-male's initiation, c1983; TR_132_ (Box 129-155)
  - She-male secretary, c1983; TR_133_ (Box 129-155)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist.
  - His sister's dress-up doll, c1983; TR_134_ (Box 129-155)
  - Her husband's panty fetish, c1983; TR_135_ (Box 129-155)
  - Stockbroker's secret life, c1983; TR_136_ (Box 129-155)
  - Mom's trained she-male, c1984; TR_137_ (Box 129-155)
  - Petticoats for a bad boy, c1984; TR_138_ (Box 129-155)
  - She-male street whore, c1984; TR_139_ (Box 129-155)
  - Dressing up daddy, c1984; TR_140_ (Box 129-155)
  - Big brother in lace, c1984; TR_141_ (Box 129-155)
  - Daddy's secret shame, c1984; TR_142_ (Box 129-155)
  - The coach wore dresses, c1984; TR_143_ (Box 129-155)
    Inventory label (?) on back cover: 27.
  - Madame's trained slave, c1984; TR_144_ (Box 129-155)
  - A father's shame, c1984; TR_145_ (Box 129-155)
  - Her little girl, c1984; TR_146_ (Box 129-155)
  - Lumberjack in lace, c1984; TR_147_ (Box 129-155)
  - Mother's strange lover, c1984; TR_148_ (Box 129-155)
  - High heeled husband, c1984; TR_149_ (Box 129-155)
  - A bra for Bobby, c1984; TR_150_ (Box 129-155)
  - Boys will be girls, c1984; TR_151_ (Box 129-155)
  - Daddy in drag, c1984; TR_152_ (Box 129-155)
  - Trucker's sweet shame, c1985; TR_153_ (Box 129-155)
    Fragmentary stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist. [?]
  - Jock in jewels, c1985; TR_154_ (Box 129-155)
  - Barbara with balls, c1985; TR_155_ (Box 129-155)
  - Pretty panty Marine, c1985; TR_156_ (Box 156-181)
  - Larry in lace, c1985; TR_157_ (Box 156-181)
  - Pretty panties, c1985; TR_158_ (Box 156-181)
  - Ribbons rope, c1985; TR_159_ (Box 156-181)
  - Training Bobby, c1985; TR_160_ (Box 156-181)
  - Jock in lace, c1985; TR_161_ (Box 156-181)
  - Making up daddy, c1985; TR_162_ (Box 156-181)
    Fragmentary stamp on top edge: [Model D]ist. [?]
  - He-man in heels, c1985; TR_163_ (Box 156-181)
  - Her brother's panties, c1985; TR_164_ (Box 156-181)
  - Movie star in lace, c1985; TR_165_ (Box 156-181)
  - Marine in panties, c1985; TR_166_ (Box 156-181)
  - Tony wears a dress, c1985; TR_167_ (Box 156-181)
  - His lingerie lust, c1985; TR_168_ (Box 156-181)
  - Panties for daddy, c1985; TR_169_ (Box 156-181)
  - Janet's frilly stud, c1985; TR_170_ (Box 156-181)
  - Barry's new bra, c1985; TR_171_ (Box 156-181)
    Ms. nos. on top edge: 11-21
  - She made him do it, c1985; TR_172_ (Box 156-181)
  - Her lover wore lace, c1986; TR_173_ (Box 156-181)
  - Jake's frilly panties, c1986; TR_174_ (Box 156-181)
  - Macho man in heels, c1986; TR_175_ (Box 156-181)
  - Black stud's lingerie, c1986; TR_176_ (Box 156-181)
  - Lace panty sergeant, c1986; TR_177_ (Box 156-181)
  - Larry's spiked heels, c1986; TR_178_ (Box 156-181)
  - Hot fireman in drag, c1986; TR_179_ (Box 156-181)
  - Her big nellie husband, c1986; TR_180_ (Box 156-181)
  - Black stud in drag, c1986; TR_181_ (Box 156-181)
  - The sailor's panties, c1986; TR_182_ (Box 182-210)
  - Her husband's lingerie, c1986; TR_183_ (Box 182-210)
  - Dressing up Billy, c1986; TR_184_ (Box 182-210)
  - Mario in make-up, c1986; TR_185_ (Box 182-210)
    Price label on front cover, partially obscuring title: 40 patn 2 $3.95.
  - High-heeled macho stud, c1986; TR_186_ (Box 182-210)
  - Bobby's new panties, c1986; TR_187_ (Box 182-210)
  - Kevin's hot lips, c1986; TR_188_ (Box 182-210)
  - The pimp wore dresses, c1986; TR_189_ (Box 182-210)
  - Banker's secret lust, c1986; TR_190_ (Box 182-210)
  - Stud in lace, c1986; TR_191_ (Box 182-210)
  - Satin nights, c1986; TR_192_ (Box 182-210)
  - Christopher's kinky kicks, c1987; TR_197_ (Box 182-210)
  - Bobby and the baroness, c1987; TR_198_ (Box 182-210)
  - Geoffrey's secret need, c1987; TR_199_ (Box 182-210)
  - The newlywed's experiment, c1987; first printing 1981; TR_200_ (Box 182-210)
  - Silka, TV stewardess, c1987; TR_201_ (Box 182-210)
  - Cumming in the country, c1987; TR_202_ (Box 182-210)
  - The trisexual connection, c1987; TR_203_ (Box 182-210)
  - Satin slaves, c1987; first printing 1982; TR_204_ (Box 182-210)
  - Cocks in white satin, c1987; TR_205_ (Box 182-210)
  - Coach drag, c1987; TR_206_ (Box 182-210)
  - Bobby in frills, c1987; TR_207_ (Box 182-210)
  - Momma's boy-girl, c1987; first printing 1982; TR_208_ (Box 182-210)
  - For the love of lace, c1987; TR_209_ (Box 182-210)
  - Billy's frillies, c1987; TR_210_ (Box 182-210)
    "Stamp on top edge: FHB EFJ [?]. Barcod label affixed to back cover, obscuring some text."
  - Inside Peter's panties, c1987; TR_211_ (Box 211-224)
    "Stamp on top edge: FHB EFJ [?]. Barcod label affixed to back cover, partially obscuring ill.."
  - The man in silk, c1987; first printing 1981; TR_212_ (Box 211-224)
  - Three way stretch, c1988; TR_213_ (Box 211-224)
  - He, she she, c1988; TR_214_ (Box 211-224)
  - Orgy for three, c1988; TR_215_ (Box 211-224)
  - Petticoat discipline, c1988; first printing 1981; TR_216_ (Box 211-224)
  - Tight friends, c1988; TR_217_ (Box 211-224)
  - Three on a couch, c1988; TR_218_ (Box 211-224)
    Barcode label affixed to p. 56.
  - His neighbor his wife, c1988; TR_219_ (Box 211-224)
    Stamp on top edge: 10.
  - Cross-dressed executives, c1988; first printing 1981; TR_220_ (Box 211-224)
  - Two nurses a doc, c1988; TR_221_ (Box 211-224)
    "Inventory label affixed to front cover: 7/03/88 407046 Price label affixed to front cover: Atn 3.95"
  - Training their stud, c1988; TR_222_ (Box 211-224)
  - Harry, Barry Jill, c1988; TR_223_ (Box 211-224)
  - Teen swinger, c1988; first printing 1985; TR_224_ (Box 211-224)
    Stamp on bottom edge: 22.